Senate fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Senate subject files, 1968 - 1984; F-84-3; 38 cm of textual records
  - Introduction of the Chairman system papers, vol. 1. modified July 1969, vol. 1, F-84-3-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 84-111)
  - Introduction of the Chairman system papers, vol. 2. modified July 1970, vol. 2, 1969; F-84-3-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 84-111)
  - Appointment of the Dean of Graduate Studies, vol. 1, vol. 1, 1969 - 1970; F-84-3-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 84-112)
  - Appointment of the Dean of Graduate Studies, vol. 2, vol. 2, 1970 - 1971; F-84-3-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 84-112)
  - Co-operative Education, vol. 1, vol. 1, 1977 - 1978; F-84-3-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 84-112)
  - Co-operative Education, vol. 2, vol. 2, 1977 - 1978; F-84-3-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 84-112)
  - Extended Studies diploma - multiple undergraduate degrees (Book 1), vol. 1. Oct. 22, 1979, vol. 1, F-84-3-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 84-112)
  - Extended Studies diploma - multiple undergraduate degrees (Book 1), vol. 2. June 11, 1979, vol. 2, F-84-3-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 84-112)
  - Extended Studies diploma - multiple undergraduate degrees (Book 1), vol. 3. Jan. 19, 1979, vol. 3, F-84-3-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 84-112)
  - Extended Studies diploma - multiple undergraduate degrees (Book 2), vol. 1, vol. 1, 1976 - 1977; F-84-3-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 84-113)
  - Extended Studies diploma - multiple undergraduate degrees (Book 2), vol. 2, vol. 2, 1977 - 1980; F-84-3-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 84-113)
  - Extended Studies diploma - multiple undergraduate degrees (Book 2), vol. 3, vol. 3, 1976 - 1980; F-84-3-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 84-113)
  - Reorganization of faculties, vol. 1, vol. 1, 1984; F-84-3-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 84-113)
  - Reorganization of faculties, vol. 2, vol. 2, 1984; F-84-3-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 84-113)
  - Reorganization of faculties, vol. 3, vol. 3, 1984; F-84-3-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 84-113)
- Senate Archives reference files, 1964 - 1996; F-84-4; 50 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records collected by the staff of the University Archives to document the organization and functioning of the Senate over the years. While these files do not constitute the official records of Senate, they are useful for historical reference.
  Records include lists of Senate members and Senate committee members, Senate handbooks, compilations of Senate rules, and summaries and reports of Senate actions.
  - Senate members, 1965 - 1993; F-84-4-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-114)
  - Senate reports, 1966 - 1967; F-84-4-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 84-114)
  - Senate rules amended, updated and edited to 1982, 1966 - 1982; F-84-4-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 84-114)
  - Senate handbook., 1988 - 1996; F-84-4-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 84-114)
  - Senate papers index, 1992 - 1993; F-84-4-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 84-114)
  - Senate summary, 1971 - 1973; F-84-4-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 84-114)
  - Senate summary, 1974 - 1978; F-84-4-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 84-114)
  - Senate summary, 1979 - 1983; F-84-4-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 84-114)
  - Senate summary, 1984 - 1986; F-84-4-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 84-114)
  - Senate summary, 1987 - 1989; F-84-4-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 84-114)
  - Senate summary, 1990 - 1994; F-84-4-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 84-114)
  - Senate and related committees, 1965; F-84-4-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 84-115)
  - Senate and related committees, 1966; F-84-4-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 84-115)
  - Senate and related committees, 1968; F-84-4-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 84-115)
  - Senate and related committees, 1969; F-84-4-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 84-115)
  - Senate and related committees, 1970; F-84-4-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 84-115)
  - Senate and related committees, 1971; F-84-4-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 84-115)
  - Senate and related committees, 1972; F-84-4-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 84-115)
  - Senate and related committees, 1973; F-84-4-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 84-115)
  - Senate and related committees, 1974; F-84-4-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 84-115)
  - Senate and related committees, 1975; F-84-4-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 84-115)
  - Senate and related committees, 1976; F-84-4-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 84-115)
  - Senate and related committees, 1977; F-84-4-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 84-115)
  - Senate and related committees, 1978; F-84-4-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 84-115)
  - Senate and related committees, 1979; F-84-4-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 84-115)
  - Senate and related committees, 1980; F-84-4-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 84-115)
  - Senate and related committees, 1981; F-84-4-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 84-116)
  - Senate and related committees, 1982; F-84-4-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 84-116)
  - Senate and related committees, 1983; F-84-4-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 84-116)
  - Senate and related committees, 1984; F-84-4-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 84-116)
  - Senate and related committees, 1985; F-84-4-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 84-116)
  - Senate and related committees, 1986; F-84-4-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 84-116)
  - Senate and related committees, 1987; F-84-4-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 84-116)
  - Senate and related committees, 1988; F-84-4-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 84-116)
  - Senate and related committees, 1989; F-84-4-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 84-116)
  - Senate and related committees, 1990; F-84-4-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 84-116)
  - Senate and related committees, 1991; F-84-4-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 84-116)
  - Senate and related committees, 1992; F-84-4-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 84-116)
  - Senate and related committees. 1993, 1996, F-84-4-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 84-116)
  - Senate Committee on Graudate Studies - papers on origin, 1964 - 1970; F-84-4-0-0-40 (Archival box - small 84-117)
  - Senate Committee on Examinations and Grading - meetings and papers, 1966; F-84-4-0-0-41 (Archival box - small 84-117)
  - Senate Graduate Admissions Board, 1967 - 1969; F-84-4-0-0-42 (Archival box - small 84-117)
  - Assessment Committee on New Graduate Studies - Communication, Earth Sciences. 1972, 1986, F-84-4-0-0-43 (Archival box - small 84-117)